Guide to the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) National Office Records WAG.281
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Locals
  This series consists of correspondence, meeting minutes, arbitrations, and local negotiations documenting the National Office's interactions with AFTRA's many local offices. AFTRA began with local union branches in New York and Los Angeles and later added additional local offices around the country to represent its members in all of the major radio and later television markets. The locals established their own governing bodies not only to represent the interests of the national union and enforce national policy, but also to respond to their constituents' needs and express and independent voice, which are shown through these records.
  - Atlanta: AFRA Applications, 1940-1952 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Atlanta: (Charlotte, NC) AFRA Applications, 1939-1950 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Atlanta: (Raleigh, NC) AFRA Applications, 1942-1950 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Atlanta: Atlanta Talent Guide AFTRA/SAG, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Atlanta: Augusta National, Inc. vs AFTRA et al. case, 1967 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Atlanta: Constitution and By-Laws, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Atlanta: Constitution and By-Laws, 1983 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Atlanta: Correspondence, 1960-1969 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Atlanta: Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Atlanta: Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Atlanta: Correspondence, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Atlanta: Correspondence, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Atlanta: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Atlanta: Correspondence, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Atlanta: Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - Atlanta: Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Atlanta: Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - Atlanta: Correspondence, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - Atlanta: Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 76, Folder 31)
  - Atlanta: Correspondence, Raleigh, NC Chapter, 1950-1963 (Box 76, Folder 32)
  - Atlanta: Correspondence re: Belue, Ray and Associates, 1974-1978 (Box 76, Folder 33)
  - Atlanta: Correspondence, Savannah, GA, 1952, 1963 (Box 76, Folder 34)
  - Atlanta: Georgia Regional Contracts 1976-1979 (Box 76, Folder 35)
  - Atlanta: Unfair Actions (from Binder), 1968-1979 (Box 76, Folder 36)
  - Boston: Accountants' Report, 1937 (Box 76, Folder 37)
  - Boston: Agreements: Capital Cities Communications, Inc., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 38)
  - Boston: AFRA Applications, 1946-1948 (Box 76, Folder 39)
  - Boston: AFRA Applications (Burlington, VT), 1946-1947 (Box 76, Folder 40)
  - Boston: AFRA Applications (Lawrence, MA), 1941 (Box 76, Folder 41)
  - Boston: AFRA Applications (Providence, RI), 1942 (Box 76, Folder 42)
  - Boston: AFRA Applications (Springfield, MA), 1945-1946 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Boston: AFTRA/SAG Talent Guide, 1990-1993 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Boston: Arbitrations: Westinghouse, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Boston: Boston/New York Member Transfers, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Boston: Broadcast News Essay by Sylvester, Jon H., WZOU-FM vs AFTRA case, News Clippings, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Boston: Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Boston: Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Boston: Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Boston: Correspondence, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Boston: Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Boston: Correspondence, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Boston: Correspondence, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Boston: Correspondence, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Boston: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Boston: Correspondence, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Boston: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Boston: Correspondence, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Boston: Correspondence, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Boston: Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Boston: Correspondence, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Boston: Correspondence, AFTRA-SAG New Englander, 1982 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Boston: Correspondence, AFTRA Regulations Governing Agents, 1985-1986 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Boston: Correspondence, AFTRA vs Total Communications Arbitration, Inc., AFTRA-SAG New Englander, 1985-1988 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Boston: "Labor in the Media in the 80's", Media Labor Law Seminar, Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Boston: New Antitrust Developments Affecting Labor Law, Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Boston: Talent and Rate Guide (AFTRA/SAG), 1987-1989 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Boston: "Theatrical Fogs and Smokes", WBZ-TV and WBZ-AM vs AFTRA case, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Boston: Unfair Actions (from Binder), Correspondence, 1964-1965, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Boston: WGBH American Labor History Series, Proposal to the National Endowment for the Humanities, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - Buffalo: AFRA Applications, 1950-1952 (Box 77, Folder 30)
  - Buffalo: Correspondence, 1981-1991 (Box 77, Folder 31)
  - Buffalo: National Labor Relations Board, Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 77, Folder 32)
  - Chicago: AFRA Applications (Des Moines, IA), 1938 (Box 77, Folder 33)
  - Chicago: AFRA Applications (Green Bay, WI), 1940 (Box 77, Folder 34)
  - Chicago: AFRA Applications (Kenosha, WI), 1949 (Box 77, Folder 35)
  - Chicago: AFRA Applications (La Crosse, WI), 1948 (Box 77, Folder 36)
  - Chicago: AFRA Applications (Madison, WI), 1937-1952 (Box 77, Folder 37)
  - Chicago: AFRA Applications (Milwaukee, WI), 1950 (Box 77, Folder 38)
  - Chicago: AFRA Applications (Sioux City, IA), 1948-1952 (Box 77, Folder 39)
  - Chicago: AFTRA Code of Fair Practice, Network Television, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 40)
  - Chicago: AFTRA Proposals for Chicago, Television Code, April 21, 1958 (Box 77, Folder 41)
  - Chicago: AFTRA/SAG Wages and Working Conditions Committee, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 42)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 43)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, Correspondence, 1979, 1985-1986 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, Correspondence, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, Correspondence (Network News Correspondents), 1985 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, Correspondence (Playback Chicago), 1987 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, Correspondence (Chicago AFTRA Newsletter), 1988 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Chicago: Board Minutes, Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Chicago: Code of Fair Practice for Television, AFRA Constitution, Announcers-Newspersons Agreement, 1973-1979 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, Jan 1971 - Jul 1971 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, Aug 1971 - Dec 1971 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, 1972 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, 1967 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Chicago: Correspondence (Notice of Appeals), 1967-1968 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, 1975 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Chicago: Correspondence (Green Bay, WI), Mar 1972 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Chicago: Correspondence (Madison, WI), 1950-1969 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, Minutes (Milwaukee, WI), 1950-1963 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, AFTRA vs WISN Radio (Milwaukee, WI), 1964-1970 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, Code of Fair Practice (Milwaukee, WI), 1971-1972 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Chicago: Correspondence, "State of the Union" Report (Milwaukee, WI), 1974-1976 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Chicago: Dells vs 20th Century Fox case, Correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Chicago: Financial Report, 1938 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Chicago: International Federation of Actors, 1975 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Chicago: Kennedy, Donald Appeal to National Board, 1984 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Chicago: McDonald Davis and Assoc. Correspondence (Milwaukee, WI), 1987-1989 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Chicago: Mitchell, Betty Memorial Fund, Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Chicago: Playback Chicago, undated (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Chicago: Racine-Kenosha Correspondence, 1962-1970 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Chicago: Racine-Kenosha Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Chicago: Sample Application Forms, Benefits Booklet, Local Code, Newsletter (Milwaukee, WI), 1975 (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - Chicago: Schedule of Rates for Network Radio Program, 1953-1968 (Box 98, Folder 14a)
  - Chicago: Television; Radio, Staff Announcers, Agreements, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - Chicago: Unfair Actions (from Binder), 1960-1978 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Chicago: Wages Report, Oct 1992 - Dec 1992 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Chicago: WTMJ vs AFTRA case, Correspondence (Milwaukee, WI), 1973 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Cleveland: AFRA Applications, 1939-1947 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Cleveland: AFTRA Television and Radio Commercials Code of Fair Practice, 1991-1994 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Cleveland: AFTRA Television and Radio Code of Fair Practice, 1974-1977 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Cleveland: AFTRA vs WJW Case and Arbitration, 1975-1979 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Cleveland: Code of Fair Practice, Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, Jan 1967 - May 1967 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, Jun 1967 - Dec 1967 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, Jan 1968 - Jul 1968 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, Aug 1968 - Dec 1968 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, Jan 1972 - May 1972 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, Jun 1972 - Nov 1972 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence (includes additional Code of Fair Practice, AFTRA vs WJW case), Jan 1974 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, Feb 1974 - Jan 1975 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, Feb 1975 - Dec 1975 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1977 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence ( includes additional WJKW vs AFTRA case), 1981 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1983 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, Jan 1985 - Jun 1985 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, Jul 1985 - Dec 1985 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence ("AFTRA Thoughts..."), 1986 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence (Briefings), Jan 1989 - Mar 1989 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence (AFTRA Local Newsletter, Briefings), Apr 1989 - Dec 1989 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Cleveland: Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Cleveland: Financial Report, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Cleveland: Labor Organizations Negligent Acts, Errors and Omissions Liability Insurance, WJKW vs AFTRA case, Correspondence, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Cleveland: National Broadcasting Co., Inc vs AFTRA case, NBC Benefits, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Cleveland: National Labor Relations Board, WERE Radio vs AFTRA case, 1986 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Cleveland: Organizing File for AFTRA Local, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Cleveland: Storer Arbitration, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Cleveland: Storer Broadcasting vs AFTRA case, Sep 1975 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Cleveland: Storer Profit Sharing Plan Booklet, ca. 1975 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Cleveland: Talent Guide (AFTRA), 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Cleveland: Talent Guide (AFTRA), 1983-1984 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Cleveland: Unfair Actions (from Binder), 1965-1979 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Dallas: AFRA Applications, 1949-1951 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Dallas: Budget Inquiries, Office Equipment Updates, Computer Reports, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Code of Fair Practice, Minimum Rate], Jan 1969 - May 1969 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Minimum Rates], Jun 1969 - Aug 1969 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Minutes Times Herald Printing vs AFTRA case], Sep 1969 - Dec 1969 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Letters of Adherence], Jan 1970 - Jul 1970 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Minutes], Aug 1970 - Dec 1970 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Minutes], Jan 1971 - May 1971 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Minimum Rate and Code of Fair Practices], Jun 1971 - Dec 1971 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Minutes], Jan 1972 - Mar 1972 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Minutes, Letters of Adherence], Apr 1972 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Regional Contracts], May 1972 - Jul 1972 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Regional Contract, Minutes], Aug 1972 - Dec 1972 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Jingles Agreements], 1977 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Minutes, Regional Contracts], Jan 1973 - Apr 1973 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Minutes], May 1973 - Dec 1973 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Minutes], Jan 1974 - Apr 1974 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Minutes], May 1974 - Dec 1974 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Minutes], Jan 1975 - May 1975 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Dallas: Correspondence, Jun 1975 - Dec 1975 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Minutes], 1976 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Dallas: Correspondence, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Regional Contract], 1978 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Dallas: Correspondence, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Dallas: Correspondence, 1980 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Dallas: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Dallas: Correspondence, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Dallas: Correspondence, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Dallas: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Dallas: Correspondence, Jan 1985 - May 1985 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Dallas: Correspondence, Jun 1985 - Dec 1985 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Dallas: Correspondence, Jan 1986 - Feb 1986 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [KDFW, Board of Directors], Mar 1986 - Dec 1986 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Member Report, Change to Discipline of Members], 1987 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Dalheim, Edward W. vs KDFW case], 1988 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Dallas: Correspondence, Jan 1989 - Apr 1989 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Dallas: Correspondence, May 1989 - Dec 1989 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Dallas: Correspondence [Becker London Kossow and Jaffe Briefings, Contracts], 1990 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Dallas: Dalheim, Edward V. vs KDFW case, Member Report, Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Dallas: Dawson, Kim Agency, Inc., Correspondence, Minutes, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Dallas: Financial Report, 1990-1992 (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - Dallas: Minutes, 1970-1973 (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - Dallas: National Labor Relations Board, KDFW cases, Gannaway-Rubenstein cases, 1985 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Dallas: Organizing Efforts: Austin, KNOW Radio, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Dallas: Organizing Efforts: Beaumont, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Dallas: Proposed Constitution Changes to Rules of Procedure, Nov 13, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Dallas: Regional Contracts, Correspondence, 1972, 1974 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Dallas: Regional Contracts, Constitution, Member Report, 1972-1978, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Dallas: Staff Procedurals Manual, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Dallas: Texas Regional Code, 1982-1985 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Dallas: Unfair Actions (from Binder), 1970-1978 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Denver: AFRA Applications, 1938-1952 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Denver: AFRA Applications (Pueblo, CO), 1947-1950 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Denver: AFRA Applications (Salt Lake City, UT), 1946-1949 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Denver: Agents, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Denver: Agreements (GE Broadcasting), 1983-1986 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Denver: Correspondence (Salt Lake City, UT), 1960-1972 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Denver: Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Denver: Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Denver: Correspondence (includes GE Strike), 1968 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Denver: Correspondence, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Denver: Correspondence, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Denver: Correspondence (includes Contest Over Jurisdiction w/ IBEW), Jan 1971 - Apr 1971 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Denver: Correspondence, May 1971 - Dec 1971 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Denver: Correspondence (Limited Letter of Adherence), 1972 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - Denver: Correspondence, Jan 1973 - Sep 1973 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - Denver: Correspondence, Oct 1973 - Dec 1973 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Denver: Correspondence, Jan 1974 - Mar 1974 (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Denver: Correspondence, Apr 1974 - Dec 1974 (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Denver: Correspondence, Jan 1975 - Jul 1975 (Box 84, Folder 28)
  - Denver: Correspondence, Aug 1975 - Sep 1975 (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - Denver: Correspondence, Oct 1975 - Dec 1975 (Box 84, Folder 30)
  - Denver: Correspondence, Jan 1976 - Mar 1976 (Box 84, Folder 31)
  - Denver: Correspondence, Apr 1976 - Aug 1976 (Box 84, Folder 32)
  - Denver: Correspondence (Board Notes from 1st Meeting of Board of Directors), Sep 1976 - Dec 1976 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Denver: Correspondence, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Denver: Correspondence (Limited Letter of Adherence), 1978 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Denver: Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Denver: Correspondence (Limited Letter of Adherence, Constitution), 1982-1983 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Denver: Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Denver: Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Denver: Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Denver: Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Detroit: AFRA Applications, 1947-1952 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Detroit: AFTRA/SAG Merger Agreements, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Detroit: Broadcast Unit, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Detroit: Broadcast Unit, 1989 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Detroit: Broadcast Unit, Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Detroit: Correspondence (Constitution), 1964 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, 1965 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Detroit: Correspondence (WWJ vs AFTRA case, AFTRA Local Magazine), 1967 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Detroit: Correspondence (AFTRA vs WJBK case, WXYZ Strike), 1970 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, 1975 (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, (WXYZ vs AFTRA case, WSPD vs AFTRA case), 1976 (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Detroit: Correspondence (National Labor Relations Board), 1977 (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - Detroit: Correspondence (Union Proposals), 1979 (Box 85, Folder 29)
  - Detroit: Correspondence (CLKW), 1980 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Detroit: Correspondence (WXYZ Arbitration), 1982 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, Dec 1983 - 1984 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Detroit: Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Detroit: Disciplinary Hearings, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Detroit: Equal Opportunity Surveys, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Detroit: Fields, Artie vs AFTRA case, Transcribed Telephone Conversations (1 of 2), 1971-1975 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Detroit: Fields, Artie vs AFTRA case, Transcribed Telephone Conversations, Correspondence (2 of 2), 1971-1974 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Detroit: Financial Information, 1967-1987 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Detroit: Financial Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Detroit: Horizon Heritage Plaza Office Lease, Sep 27, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Detroit: IATSE Strike at WJBK, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Detroit: Minutes, Correspondence, 1969-1977 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Detroit: National Labor Relations Board, J.L. Hudson vs SAG/AFTRA case, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Detroit: National Labor Relations Board, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - Detroit: Talent and Rate Guide, 1984-1985 (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - Detroit: Unfair Actions (from Binder), Correspondence, 1963-1978 (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - Detroit: Union Town: A Labor History Guide to Detroit, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - Fresno: Constitution and By-Laws, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - Fresno: Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - Fresno: Correspondence, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - Fresno: Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 86, Folder 29)
  - Fresno: Correspondence, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 30)
  - Fresno: Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 86, Folder 31)
  - Fresno: Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 86, Folder 32)
  - Fresno: Correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 86, Folder 33)
  - Fresno: Correspondence, KJEO, AFTRA vs RETLAW, Mar 1991 - Sep 1991 (Box 86, Folder 34)
  - Fresno: Correspondence, KJEO, AFTRA vs RETLAW, Oct 1991 - Dec 1991 (Box 86, Folder 35)